module.exports.quiz = [
    {
      question: "India's first-ever national police museum will establish in which city?",
      answers: {
        a: "Chennai",
        b: "Delhi",
				c: "Nagpur",
        d: "Kolkata"
      },
      answer: "b"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country will host the 45th G7 summit 2019?",
      answers: {
        a: "Italy",
        b: "Germany",
        c: "France",
				d: "Canada"
      },
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country's women cricket team has clinched the Asia Cup Twenty-20 tournament 2018?",
      answers: {
        a: "South Korea",
        b: "Bangladesh",
        c: "India",
        d: "Pakistan"
      },
      answer: "b"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has won the men's singles French Open tennis tournament 2018?",
      answers: {
        a: "Novak Djokovic",
        b: "Dominic Thiem",
        c: "Roger Federer",
        d: "Rafael Nadal"
      },
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country's football team has lifted the 2018 Intercontinental Cup football title?",
      answers: {
        a: "India",
        b: "Sri Lanka",
        c: "Kenya",
        d: "Argentina"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following personalities from India is the only winner of Special Oscar in the history of Indian Cinema so far?",
      answers: {
        a: "Mrinal Sen",
        b: "Shyam Bengal",
        c: "Satyajit Ray",
        d: "Mira Nair"
      },
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "Who wrote Arthashastra?",
      answers: {
        a: "Kalhan",
        b: "Visakhadatta",
        c: "Bana Bhatta",
        d: "Chanakya"
      },
      answer: "d"
    },
		{
			question: "H.J. Kania was the first...",
			answers: {
				a: "Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of India",
				b: "Attorney-General of India",
				c: "Solicitor-General of India",
				d: "None of them"
			},
			answer: "a"
		},
    {
      question: "Which is the world's largest dry desert?",
      answers: {
        a: "Sahara",
        b: "Thar of Desert",
        c: "Black Rock Desert",
        d: "Gobi Desert"
      },
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best conductor of electricity?",
      answers: {
        a: "Salt water",
        b: "Green water",
        c: "Cold water",
        d: "sweet water"
      },
      answer: "a"
    }
];
